

aelichung@gmail.com (626) 348-9900 anne-elise.me Santa Clara, CA

TOOLS & KNOW-HOW

UX Design

Draw.io, Balsamiq, User flows. User stories

Front-end Development

HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Firebase, Git

Digital Prototyping/Research

Sketch, Figma, Invision, Usabilityhub, Maze

Adobe CC

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Lightroom, Premiere

Tech. Design & Rendering

AutoCAD, Rhino, SketchUp, Revit, V-Ray, Maxwell, Artlantis

Physical Prototyping & Mock-ups

3D printing, lasercutting, working with wood/metal/plaster/resin etc.

PROJECTS

UX UI & FRONT-END 2018 (8 weeks)

houseplant

An online plant store for people with black thumbs.

I designed, tested, and developed an e-commerce site to help people plant shop confidently.

Case Study: https://anne-elise.me/case-studies/houseplant.html

Prototype: https://aelichung.github.io/houseplant/

UX DESIGN & RESEARCH 2018-present

Renter's Rights Guide

An ongoing project to guide San José residents through their rights as a tenant. Working with a team of 5, I created wireframes and prototypes, and conducted usability tests.

UI & CONSTRUCTION 2015 (10 weeks)

Striptease

I worked in a team of 20 to create a provocative installation, blending both physical and digital design. I lead the design for the user interface, as well as helping with construction and design. The installation show was attended by over a hundred people and warmly received.

More Info (click on the striptease gallery link): https://anne-elise.me/work.html

Video: https://youtu.be/j8MizHxy8-4?t=26s

EDUCATION

DESIGN PROGRAM

2017-present

BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURE 2010–2015

Bloc

California Polytechnic State University San Luis Obispo

WORK EXPERIENCE

CAD CONSULTANT 2017-present

WDA (Warner Design Associates)

Providing CAD training, project support and technical assistance.

TECHNICAL DESIGNER 2015–2017

EDG Interior Architecture and Design

Worked with construction, engineers, and clients to create luxury hotel and restaurant spaces.

SERVICE

VOLUNTEER UX / UI / FRONT-END 2018-present

VOLUNTEER TUTOR 2018-present

Code for San Jose